Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 19.04.25 17:25:49
- [children shouting, chattering] - [dog barking]
[siren wailing, faint]
[siren continues wailing, faint]
注意 近日移除
[siren continues wailing, louder]
- [siren continues wailing, louder] - [water dripping]
塞西利亚是第一个
[man narrating] Cecilia was the first to go.
[siren continues wailing, louder]
[siren stops wailing]
[ambulance radio chatter, indistinct]
[water draining from tub]
[monitor beeping]
[siren wailing]
[door closes]
你怎么弄成这样?       宝贝
What are you doing here, honey?
你还小未经世事
You're not even old enough to know how bad life gets.
显然 医生
Obviously, Doctor, you've never been a 13-year-old girl.
你从未当过13岁的女孩
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
处女之死
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：夜明珠  校对：Otherbreath
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：麦麦
每个人都记得我们的邻居
[narrator] Everyone dates the demise of our neighborhood
里斯本女孩们自杀的日子
from the suicides of the Lisbon girls.
人们在无精打采的榆树
People saw their clairvoyance in the wiped-out elms,
密歇根州 25年前
the harsh sunlight,
和日渐衰落的汽车工业中瞥见她们犀利的眼神
and the continuing decline of our auto industry.
年少的我们试着把碎片拼贴完整
Even then, as teenagers, we tried to put the pieces together.
仍是失败了
We still can't.
现在每当我们在商务餐会或鸡尾派对上相遇
Now, whenever we run into each other at business lunches or cocktail parties,
都会不由得在角落里重温那些证据
we find ourselves in the corner going over the evidence one more time.
只为了解那五个女孩
All to understand those five girls...
经过这么多年 她们仍铭刻在我们的脑海
who, after all these years, we can't get out of our minds.
塞西利亚 最小的一个 13岁
Cecilia, the youngest, was 13.
勒克斯 14岁
And Lux was 14.
邦妮 15岁
Bonnie was 15.
玛丽 16岁
Mary was 16.
特瑞丝17岁
And Therese was 17.
没人明白我们的数学老师
No one could understand how Mrs. Lisbon and Mr. Lisbon, our math teacher,
里斯本先生和她夫人
had produced such beautiful creatures.
怎么会造出这么美丽的尤物
保罗・巴蒂诺说
Paul Baldino claimed to have found Cecilia on her first attempt.
塞西利亚的初次自杀是他发现的
是我发现她的
Hey, I was the one who found her.
我站在我家的下水道里
[exhales] I was in the storm sewer under my house,
你能从那儿进入任何人的家
and there's all these tunnels.
我们信以为真
You can get into anyone's house.
[narrator] So when Paul said this, we believed him
因为他爸是美国大兵 鲨鱼巴蒂诺
because he was the son of Sammy "The Shark" Baldino,
我们知道他的逃生隧道经过下水道
and we knew about his escape tunnel that led through the sewers.
我是想去
So I went up, thinkin' I could see one of those Lisbon girls takin' a shower.
看她们洗澡
对 是的
- Yeah. - All right.
接着我进去了...到处都是血!
And I walk in...
and I see blood everywhere.
所以我转身 顺着隧道原路返回
So I turned around and went straight for the stairs and right back up the tunnel.
我必须告诉你们这事 回见
Had to tell you guys that story, so...
I'll see you guys later, all right?
我听说那是意外
[woman on phone] I heard it was an accident.
不 根本不是意外 只怪她父母
[woman 2] No, it was no accident, Joan. Of course the parents are to blame.
我听说他们在马桶里找到刀片
Well, I heard they found the razor in the toilet.
对塞西利亚自杀的原因 众说纷纭
[narrator] Everyone had an opinion as to why Cecilia had tried to kill herself.
她不想死
That girl didn't wanna die.
只是想从家里逃出来
She just wanted out of that house.
她想摆脱那种装潢方式
She wanted out of that decorating scheme.
[chuckles]
最流行的理论认为
[narrator] The most popular theory held Dominic Palazzolo to blame.
多米尼克・帕拉佐是罪魁祸首
多米尼克是个移民 暂时住在亲威家
Dominic was the immigrant kid who was staying with relatives
直到他的家人在新墨西哥安家
until his family got settled in New Mexico.
他是街坊里第一个戴墨镜的男孩
He was the first boy in our neighborhood to wear sunglasses,
来了还不到一周他就恋爱了
and within a week of his arrival he'd fallen in love.
他心仪的对象不是塞西利亚
[tennis ball hitting rackets]
The object of his desire wasn't Cecilia, but Diana Porter.
而是黛安娜・波特
我爱她!
[sighs]
I love her.
黛安娜去瑞士度假时 多米尼克逆天而行
When Diana Porter left on vacation in Switzerland,
Dominic denounced God.
为表真心
[boy] I don't know!
And to prove the validity of his love, he jumped off the roof of his relatives' house.
他从亲戚家的房顶跳下去了
[mouths words]
[shrubbery rustling]
[exhales]
我要给你看一些图象
[clears throat] I'm gonna show you some images.
然后... 呃 你告诉我
And, uh, you tell me...
你想到了什么
what they remind you of.
好吗?
Okay?
香蕉
A banana.
沼泽
A swamp.
爆炸头
An Afro.
Mm-hmm.
我认为塞西利亚并不真想自杀
I don't think Cecilia truly meant to end her life.
她的举动是求助的呐喊
Her act was a cry for help.
我知道你们非常严格
I know you're very strict,
但建立一些校外社交关系
but I think that Cecilia would benefit
对塞西利亚十分有益
by having a social outlet outside of the codification of school...
跟同龄的男孩交往交往
where she could interact with males her own age.
彼得帮里斯本先生
[narrator] Peter Sisten had helped Mr. Lisbon
在教室建了个太阳系模型
install a model of the solar system in his classroom,
作为回报 里斯本先生请他来吃晚饭
and in return Mr. Lisbon invited him for dinner.
保佑我们 主啊为了这些
[Mr., Mrs. Lisbon] Bless us, O Lord, in these, thy gifts
我们因耶稣之慷慨而收到的礼物 阿门
which we are about to receive from thy bounty.
Through Christ our Lord. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
勒克斯 把上衣穿上 抱歉
Lux, please. Put your shirt on this instant.
[Lux] Sorry.
谢谢 宝贝儿 把盐递过来好吗?
[Mrs. Lisbon] Thank you, dear.
[Cecilia] Can you pass the salt, please?
要火腿吗? 谢谢
- Ham? - Thank you.
甜心 要点儿豌豆吗? 我讨厌豌豆
[Mrs. Lisbon] Uh, sweetheart, would you like some peas?
- [Cecilia] I hate peas. - Here.
火腿看上去真不错 亲爱的
[Mrs. Lisbon] That's a nice-looking ham, dear.
谢谢 亲爱的 真不错 妈妈
[Mrs. Lisbon] Oh, thank you, honey.
[Bonnie] Mmm, this is good, Mom.
那么 彼得 你是个飞机狂热者吗?
So, Peter, are you, uh, an aviation enthusiast?
嗯 我不知道是否该把自己称作狂热者
- [clears throat] - Well, I, uh ―
I don't know if I'd call myself an enthusiast, but, uh, I like planes.
我喜欢飞机
- Oh, yeah? - [Cecilia] Thanks.
Ah. [chuckles]
彼得 你是橄榄球队的吗?
Uh, Peter, are you on ― on the football squad?
不 我玩儿这个 但不在队里
Um, no, I play it, but I'm not actually on the team.
哦 我知道了 不是队员
- [Mrs. Lisbon] Oh, I see. - [Mr. Lisbon] Not a team player. [chuckles]
你喜欢摔跤吗?
- Do you like to wrestle? - [coughs]
你还好吧?
- [Lux giggling] - [Mr. Lisbon] You okay, Peter?
一种巴西青蛙今天被列入濒危物种了
The Brazilian turbot frog was added to the endangered species list today.
今年的第三种了
- That's the third animal this year. - Oh, dear.
哦 宝贝儿 我头一次听说
The turbot frog. Darling, I don't think I've ever heard of it.
不好意思 我可以用一下厕所吗? 当然
Um, excuse me. May I use the restroom?
楼下的坏了
[Mrs. Lisbon] Oh, of course. The one down here isn't working very well.
去楼上塞西利亚的房间
- [clears throat] - Go upstairs, through Cecilia's room.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
卫生棉条
- [knocking] - Hold ― Hold on.
等等
我以为你死在里边了
[giggles] I thought you'd died in there.
你霸占完厕所了吗? 我需要点东西
Are you done hogging the bathroom? I need something.
介意回避一下吗?
Do you mind?
[Lux chuckles]
非常谢谢 你忘了东西
Thank you very much.
Are you forgetting something?
[laughs]
彼得 这是一片空气箔... 谢谢
Oh, Peter. Here's a little airfoil I thought you might find ―
- Thank you. - find amusing.
这是柏得利原理的应用
It's a ― [clears throat]
demonstration of Bernoulli's principle.
举起...
Lift and ― [exhales]
从那以后 里斯本家的就开始变样了
[narrator] From that time on, the Lisbon house began to change.
几乎每天
Almost every day,
甚至不用照看塞西利亚时
and even when she wasn't keeping an eye on Cecilia,
勒克斯都会穿着游泳衣 坐在毛巾上晒黑
Lux would suntan on her towel,
换来15分钟
wearing a swimsuit that caused the knife sharpener
免费磨刀演示
to give her a 15-minute demonstration for free.
遵循医嘱
Following the doctor's orders,
塞西利亚回家两周后
two weeks after Cecilia returned home,
里斯本先生说服妻子允许女孩们举办了
Mr. Lisbon persuaded his wife to allow the girls
to throw the first and only party of their short lives.
短暂人生中第一场也是唯一一场派对
好了 这样行吗?
There. Is that okay?
我得去换衣服了
I gotta get dressed.
欢迎 晚上好 里斯本太太
- Welcome. - Good evening, Mrs. Lisbon.
进来吧
Come on in.
派对在地下室
[Mrs. Lisbon] The party's in the basement.
[speakers: pop music playing, faint]
左转 下楼梯
Just go on around to the left and then down the stairs.
[speakers: new pop song playing]
[music continues playing]
嗨 我是邦妮
Hi. I'm Bonaventure.
嗨... 我是蒂姆 很高兴见到你
- Hi. - Hi. Tim.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi. - Hi.
想要点潘趣酒吗? 好的
- Would you like some punch? - Yeah.
谢谢
- Okay. - Thanks.
嗨 谢谢
- Hi. - Hi.
Thanks.
嗨 谢谢
- Hi. - Thank you.
嘿 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
想坐下吗? 好的
[Mary] Do you wanna sit down?
Yeah.
? The days and the years ?
? Will go streaking by ?
? But the time has stopped In my dream ?
? We have all our everyday Hopes and fears ?
? And you'll find no exception in me ?
? But that doesn't get me Through a sea of tears ?
? Over life's biggest tragedy ?
- ? You're so long ago ? - [girl giggling]
? And so far away ?
? But my dream lives on forever ?
[speakers: pop song continues playing]
你的智力测验分数怎么样?       还不错
Um, how'd your SAT's go?
Okay.
很好
Good.
你知道要申请哪所大学吗?
Do you know where you're applying yet?
没有 但我父母倾向于耶鲁
Well, no, but my parents are pushing towards Yale
因为那是我爸的母校 真不错
because that's where my dad went.
That's nice.
你要想象云层散开
But you have to imagine what it'd be like when the clouds would open up
亨驾驶着梅塞施米特(德国战斗机)冲出阳光
and out of the sun would come the Hun and his Messerschmitt coming down.
孩子们 大你们两三岁的
And, boys, I swear, what, two or three years older than you
都开P51-B野马式战斗机
would be in this, the P-51B Mustang.
"B"代表舷窗
"B" for what? For bull's-eye, see?
[speakers: pop song continues playing]
你听说过耶鲁吗? 是的
You've heard of Yale?
Oh, yeah.
潘趣酒真不错 再来点?
This punch is fantastic.
- Can I give you more? - Sure.
里边有什么?
What's in it?
果汁 一些樱桃... 菠萝
Juices ― some cherry, uh, pineapple.
你知道 我... 我喜欢菠萝
You know, I, uh ―
I love pineapple.
真的吗?
Really?
? You're so far away ?
? And so long ago ?
这宝贝出场了
This baby would come in ―
就是它让英国打了胜仗
And this won the war for the United Kingdom. You see?
抱歉 没事
- E-Excuse me. - Sure. Okay.
就是这个仪器让模型运转
And it's this kind of, uh ― this kind of, uh, equipment that ―
that makes, uh, a model work.
这是周
Here's Joe.
嗨 周 嗨
- [Mr. Lisbon] Hi, Joe. - Hi.
[Mary] Hi, Joe.
如果他有需要 打电话叫我
- Now, if he needs anything, just call me. - Oh, I'm sure we'll be fine.
他会没事的 I’m sure he'll be fine.
嗨 嗨
- Hi. - [girl giggling softly]
Hi.
周 很高兴见到你 你好吗?
- Joe, good to see you. - How are ya?
很高兴你今晚能来 你怎么样?
- Good. - Glad you came tonight.
- How's it going? - Hey, Joe, how's it going?
你来的正好
- You're just in time. - [Joe] In time.
嗨
Good. Hi.
看 如果你挠他下巴他耳朵就动
Hey, everyone, look. His ears wiggle if you scratch his chin.
[all laughing]
周 唱你的歌
Joe, sing your song.
三宝颜（菲律宾城市）的猴子没尾巴
? All the monkeys have no tails In Zamboanga ?
猴子没尾巴
? All the monkeys have no tails ?
被鲸鱼吃掉啦
? Got bitten off by whales ?
三宝颜的猴子没尾巴
? All the monkeys have no tails In Zamboanga ?
- [cheering, applause] - Good job, Joe. Good song.
真是首好歌 唱的好 周
Good job, Joe.
[speakers: pop ballad playing]
你从哪儿学的这首歌?
- Where'd you learn that song? - That was good.
我能离开一会儿吧?
May I be excused?
只要你想 但宝贝儿 这是你的派对
If you want to, my dear, but this is your party.
- [song continues playing] - [chattering, laughing]
好吧 如果你想上楼就去吧 我们...
A-All right, i-if you wanna go upstairs, go ahead.
But we'll just ― we'll just have to have fun without you.
我们只能在没有你的情况下玩了
看 他总是选正面
Oh, look. He always chooses heads.
周 会是哪面? 正面
- Joe, what's it gonna be? - Heads.
周 试试背面
Joe, will you try tails?
就是正面!
- Heads it is. - [chuckles]
再来 正面
Let's try again, eh? Let's go.
正面! 再来一次
- Heads. - Tails.
Heads.
在空中 周 正面
- One more time. In the air, Joe. - [Joe] Heads.
[kids laughing, chattering]
又是正面!
Heads it is anyway!
再来一次 提前猜 周 正面
One more time, man.
- Okay, call it in the air, Joe. - Heads.
- ? All I need is the air that I breathe ? - Heads. That's enough of that.
正面 真不错
? And to love you ?
你怎么样?       很好
- How ya doin'? - [laughing, chattering]
Good.
他学的真快
- Picked it up pretty well. - Yeah.
这是我最喜欢的歌
- You should have a record. - It's my favorite song.
你知道 你... 非常漂亮 像圣人一样
You know, you're very beautiful.
Say, I could paint you some time.
有时间我可以给你画像
谢谢
Thanks.
[speakers: song fades] ? All I need is the air that I breathe ?
他们唱歌了吗?
- Oh, so, did they sing it to you? - Yeah.
哇 真好!
- Wow, that's good. - [chattering, laughing]
天啊!
[Mr. Lisbon] Cecilia!
- [gasps] - [gasps]
哦 主啊!
Oh, no.
塞西利亚!
Cecilia!
[gasps]
[sobs]
哦 我的... 不 不 不!
Oh, my ― [gasps]
No! No, no, no. Don't look. Turn around.
不要看 转过去
转过去! 亲爱的 转... 我的上帝!
Turn around. Darlings, turn around.
Don't look. Don't ― Don't loo ― [gasps]
[Mrs. Lisbon] What is this?
哦 耶稣!
[whispering] Oh, Jesus. Please, God.
求你了 上帝
[Mrs. Lisbon sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[girls crying]
我们到了
[Mr. Lisbon] What do we have here now?
今天拒办葬礼
No funerals today.
[Mr. Lisbon] You in charge?
[no audible dialogue]
All right.
- Okay. - [man] Okay, fellas.
他说她才13岁
Said she was only 13.
[doorbell rings]
[man on TV] Against Kinella lifetime, 12 out of 47.
He has a home run and six runs driven in.
Kinella looks in, shakes off the sign from Delitta.
嗨 玛丽 你父母在家吗?
Oh, hi, Mary. Are your parents home?
嗨 神父 请进
[Mary] Hi, Father Moody. Come in.
Taken up high. Ball one.
你好 神父
Oh, hello, Father. [chuckles]
请坐
- Please sit down. - Inside. Ball two.
谢谢
Thanks.
拜托 那是界内球!
Come on, Miller, that was inside.
呃 不了 谢谢
Uh, no. No, thanks.
Ah.
把夫人叫下来 聊一聊好吗?
How 'bout we get the missus down here, have a little chat?
恐怕她不舒服 I’m afraid she's under the weather.
Afraid she's under the weather.
她...
[clears throat] She's not really...
谁也不见
uh, seeing anybody.
嗯 她会见牧师的
Well, she'll see her priest.
这孩子每次都打不好界内球
Ah, this kid's a sucker for the high inside ones every time.
每次都是
- Swing and a miss. Strike two. - Every time.
抱歉
Excuse me.
神父...
Father.
Swing and a ground ball to short!
Walker picks it up, makes a flip to Durand, over to Burnett!
- [chuckles] - Double play!
双杀 神父
- Double play, Father. - And that will end the inning.
双杀
Double play.
He's hitting .212 this season,
has 23 home runs, driven in 57 runs for the Dodgers.
He steps up against Kinella.
Rosenthal against Kinella lifetime, 12 out of 47.
Has a home run and six runs driven in.
里斯本太太?
- Mrs. Lisbon? - He now looks in, shakes off the sign.
[knocks lightly]
我能进来吗? 好的
May I come in?
[Therese] Okay.
你们好 女孩们 我想我们可以谈谈
Hello, girls.
I thought we could talk.
你们想聊聊吗?
Do you feel like talking?
嗯... 如果你们想的话
Well, if you ever want to, you know where to find me.
你们知道到哪儿找我
里斯本太太? 我是穆迪神父
Mrs. Lisbon, it's Father Moody.
里斯本太太 你好
Mrs. Lisbon, hello.
我想告诉你
I wanted you to know that I listed Cecilia's death as an accident.
塞西利亚的死是个意外
一场必然发生的意外
[woman murmuring] An accident waiting to happen.
他们无法自欺欺人
John said you couldn't get a policy to cover it.
真是太危险了
[woman 2] I know. It's so incredibly dangerous.
我们试试
Let's give it a try.
准备好了? 123
Ready?
One, two, three.
[woman whispers] Oh, God.
太悲伤了 真让我不敢相信
- It's just so sad, I can't even believe it. - Footings are too deep.
你车里的锁链呢?
You got that chain in your truck?
[truck engine starts]
开车!
Hit it!
我们收集的里斯本女孩的纪念品保存至今
[narrator] Our collection of souvenirs of the Lisbon girls, which still exists,
从塞西利亚的日记开始
started with Cecilia's diary.
帕克从水管工那儿弄来的
Parkie had gotten it from Skip Ortega, the plumber's assistant,
他在浴室的马桶边找到它
who had found it next to the toilet in the bathroom.
蒂姆・微纳是智者 解密了它
Tim Weiner, the brain, decoded it.
感情不稳定
Emotional instability.
看看"i"上的圆点 每个都如是
Look at the I's, the dots on 'em. They're everywhere.
基本上 她是个梦想家
Basically, what we have here is a dreamer,
一个完全与现实脱节的人
someone completely out of touch with reality.
她跳起来时 可能感觉自己要飞起来了
When she jumped, she probably thought she was flying.
Here.
2月13日 周一 今天我们吃的冰批萨
"Monday, February 13. Today we had frozen pizza.
周四 妈妈晚饭做了奶油玉米
Thursday. Mom made creamed corn for dinner.
糟透了 看上去就像...
It's the worst. It looks like ―"
玛丽像白痴一样撞烂了门牙
"Mary chipped her front tooth on the monkey bars, acting like an idiot.
她大吵大闹 还不得不去补牙
She made a big scene and had to go get her tooth capped. It looks normal, I guess."
我猜看上去没两样 给我
Here, give me that.
我就说她补过牙
I told you she had a capped tooth.
榆树! 一棵要死的树能写多少页?
Elm trees. How many pages can you write about dying trees?
这是有关多米尼克的
Here. Something about Dominic.
帕佐罗今天为了那阔绰婊子波特
"Palazzolo jumped off the roof today over that rich bitch Porter.
从屋顶上跳下来了
你还能再蠢点么?
How stupid can you be?"
今天我们乘船出海
"Today we went out on the boat. It was pretty cold.
很冷 我们看到了几只鲸鱼
勒克斯摸了鲸鱼 没想到它们这么臭
We saw a couple of whales.
Lux leaned over and stroked a whale. I didn't think they would stink so much.
是它们肚子里的海草烂了
It's the kelp in their baleens rotting.
我希望以后可以再去
I hope we can go again sometime."
读读这个吧
Hang on. Just read this. Read that.
勒克斯看上了凯文...
- "Lux lost it over Kevin..." - "Hines."
是"海兹"吗? 那个送垃圾的男人
- Is it "Hines"? The garbage man. - The garbage man.
勒克斯看上了凯文・海纳兹
[Cecilia] Lux lost it over Kevin Heines, the garbage man.
那个送垃圾的男人
她早上5点起床 在前门台阶上转悠
She'd wake up at 5:00 in the morning and hang out casually on the front steps,
就跟别人看不出来似的!
like it wasn't completely obvious.
她把他的名字写在所有的内衣上
She wrote his name in marker on all her bras and underwear.
妈妈发现了 把所有凯文的字样都漂白了
Mom found them and bleached out all the Kevins.
勒克斯在床上哭了一整天
Lux was crying on her bed all day.
[no audible dialogue]
"这些树 像充满空气的肺叶"
The trees, like lungs filling with air.
"我姐姐 恶毒的那个 拉我的头发"
My sister, the mean one, pulling my hair.
于是我们得以知晓她们的生活
[narrator] And so we started to learn about their lives...
那些记忆汇集了我们未曾经历过的时光
coming to hold collective memories of times we hadn't experienced.
我们感受到作为女孩的被禁锢感
We felt the imprisonment of being a girl,
它是如何让你变得浮想联翩
the way it made your mind active and dreamy
让你了解到哪些颜色更搭
and how you ended up knowing what colors went together.
我们知道女孩们都有着缜密的内心
We knew that the girls were really women in disguise,
她们懂得爱情 甚至死亡
that they understood love and even death,
我们能做的就是吸引她们
and that our job was merely to create the noise that seemed to fascinate them.
她们对我们了如指掌
We knew that they knew everything about us
我们对她们却一无所知
and that we couldn't fathom them at all.
嗨 里斯本太太 我是莉迪亚・皮尔 我在做... Hi. Mrs. Lisbon, I’m Lydia Perl. I’m putting together...
Hi, uh, Mrs. Lisbon. I'm Lydia Perl.
I'm putting together a ―
嗨 我是邦妮 这是玛丽 Oh! Hi, I’m Bonnie. This is Mary.
Oh.
Hi, I'm Bonnie. This is Mary.
你好 女孩们 我来问你们几个问题... Hello, girls. I’m here to ask you a couple of questions...
Hello, girls.
Um, I'm here to ask you a couple of questions, uh, about Cecilia.
是关于塞西利亚的
嗯? 好的 呃...
Yeah?
Oh, great, great.
或许你们能告诉我一点她的事?
Um, maybe you could start by, um, telling me a little bit about her.
Um, did she have any special interests or hobbies?
她有没有什么特殊的兴趣爱好?
她很喜欢写日记
Um, she liked to write in her journal a lot.
真棒
That is great.
好的 她有没...
Um, okay.
Uh, did she ― did she ever talk about ending her life?
她有说过要结束自己的生命吗?
出什么事了?
What's going on here?
你一定是里斯本太太
Um, you must be Mrs. Lisbon.
我是莉迪亚・皮尔 我为二频道做一档节目 I’m Lydia Perl. I’m doing a piece for Channel Two.
I'm Lydia Perl. I'm doing a piece for Channel 2 and ―
这儿不欢迎你 皮尔小姐
You have to leave now, Miss Perl.
去年夏天 东部一位自杀少女
The suicide of an east-side teenager last summer
引发了国民危机意识
has increased the awareness of a national crisis.
我站在塞西利亚・里斯本家门前 一个13岁... I’m at the home where Cecilia Lisbon...
I now stand in front of the home where Cecilia Lisbon, a 13-year-old...
他们为什么不让她安息呢?
Why don't they just let her rest in peace?
...爱好写诗 悲剧性的结束了自己的生命
...who liked to paint and write poetry,
tragically put an end to her life.
心理学家一致认为 当代青少年
Psychologists agree that adolescence today
比起以前
is much more fraught by pressures and complexities than in years past.
更加复杂与脆弱
越来越多的医生说挫败感能引起暴力行为
More and more doctors say that this frustration can lead to acts of violence
青少年无法将现实
whose reality the adolescent cannot separate from its intended drama.
与虚幻区分开来
我烤了一个有老鼠药的馅饼
I baked a pie full of rat poison.
我觉得我可以悄悄吃下它
I thought I could eat it, you know,
without being suspicious.
我奶奶 她都86了...
My nana, who was 86...
她真的很喜欢甜食
She really liked sweets.
她吃了三块
She had three pieces.
[sobbing]
我为这个母亲感到难过 I’m sorriest for the mother.
[woman on phone] I feel sorriest for the mother.
不 你一直想知道如何补救
[woman 2 on phone] I know.
You would always wonder if there was something you could've done.
我要挂了 再见
- [woman] Well, I gotta go. See you later. - [woman 2] All right, then.
好的 再见
- Bye-bye. - Bye.
再见
[girl singing]
[chattering, faint]
[wooden wind chimes tinkling]
别担心
Don't worry.
他们把栅栏拆了
They took the fence out.
老天 你打鼾可够响的
God, you snore loud.
[alarm buzzes, stops]
[chattering]
那些女孩有光明的前途
[woman] Those girls have a bright future ahead of them.
另一个却已成定局
The other one was just gonna end up a kook.
直到9月7号
[narrator] We didn't see the girls together as a group until convocation, September 7.
我们才见到女孩们一块出现
玛丽 勒克斯 邦妮和特瑞丝
Mary, Lux, Bonnie, and Therese
来到学校 就像什么也没发生过
came to school as though nothing had happened.
我们觉得只要仔细看
And we felt that if we kept looking hard enough,
就会明白她们的感觉以及她们到底是谁
we might begin to understand what they were feeling and who they were.
好的 正如你记得的 这是维恩图
All right, so, if we have ―
And these are Venn diagrams, as you remember.
我们有'A'和'B'相交
If we have A and B intersecting,
这是'A'跟'B'
and A and B,
如果'A'与'B'相交 就得出这块区域
if A intersects B, we have this area.
如果'A'与'B'相并
And if A is the union with B, we have all of the circle
就得出整个圆和相交部分
这就是交集和并集的规则
plus the intersection.
These are the laws of intersection and union. Okay?
过的怎么样?
How's it going?
还不错
Not bad.
好的 "素描《淑女本色》...
Okay, do a character sketch on the following characters from Portrait of a Lady.
中的一个角色..."
The first one is... Ralph.
第一个是... 罗夫
呃... 他很好
Um... he was nice.
他死时我真的很难过
It was really sad when he died.
哦 上帝 真不敢相信我刚才说了什么
Oh, my gosh. I can't believe I just said that.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
读到了惊人的自杀率
Reading about the alarming suicide rate,
我与伍德哈斯先生和其他几位老师谈过了
I talked to Mr. Woodhouse and some of the teachers here
意识到如此重大的问题
and realized that nothing about this serious matter
还未在学校里讨论过
has been discussed at this school.
随后就有绿色的小册子发下来
[narrator] And quickly thereafter, green pamphlets were distributed.
我们觉得绿色很欢快 也不算太欢快
[woman] We thought green was cheerful, but not too cheerful.
显然比红色要好
Certainly better than red.
册子里说
[narrator] The green pamphlets told us that there were 80 suicides a day in America,
美国一天有80起自杀
一年30,000起
30,000 a year...
茄子!
[all] Cheese!
这敲响了我们
...and alerted us to danger signals we couldn't help but look for.
一直在找寻的危险警报
里斯本的女孩子们瞳孔扩大了吗?
Were the Lisbon girls' pupils dilated?
她们对校园活动
Had they lost interest in school activities, in sports and hobbies?
体育运动或爱好失去兴趣了吗?
她们被同龄人孤立了吗?
Had they withdrawn from their peers?
嗨 我是瑞斯 Hi, I’m Chase.
Hi. I'm Chase.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我这辈子就上过这一所学校
I've only been going to this school my whole life.
不用没话找话说
You don't have to talk to me.
比如说 我们有两种不同的经济类型
[man] So, for example, we have two different types of economics,
第一种叫做宏观经济
or so-called two different types of economics.
Now, the first one, we would say, is called macroeconomics, which is...
看
Look. She's laughing.
她在笑
他让她笑了
He made her laugh.
这条狗嘴里哪吐得出象牙!
I never heard him say anything remotely intelligent.
与勒克斯交谈的男孩
[narrator] The boys who talked with Lux were always the stupidest boys
总是很蠢 也套不出任何信息
and made terrible sources of information.
..手风琴 她挺好
Squeezebox. She's all right.
告诉你吧 她绝对是学校里最辣的女孩
Let me tell you, she's the hottest girl in the school, for sure.
想知道发生什么了?闻我的手指吧 伙计
You wanna know what happened? Smell my fingers, man.
不 她不谈起塞西利亚
Nah, she didn't talk about Cecilia.
我们并没在说话 如果你知道我的意思
We weren't exactly talking, if you know what I mean.
认识勒克斯的唯一可靠的男孩
[narrator] But the only reliable boy who actually got to know Lux...
是崔普・方汀
was Trip Fontaine,
他最近减掉了婴儿肥
who, only eight months before the suicides, had emerged from baby fat
这很让女孩和妈妈们高兴
to the delight of girls and mothers alike.
我又迟到了
[whispers] I'm late again.
哦 拜托!
Oh, come on.
谢谢
Thank you.
[rock intro playing]
[woman] ? Cold, late night so long ago ?
? When I was not so strong, you know ?
? Pretty man came to me ?
? Never seen eyes so blue ?
? You know, I could not run away, it seemed ?
? We'd seen each other in a dream ?
? Seemed like he knew me ?
? He looked right through me ?
? Yeah ?
? "Come on home, girl" He said with a smile ?
? "You don't have to love me ?
? Yet let's get high a while" ?
? But try to understand ?
? Try to understand ?
? Try, try, try to understand ?
? He's a magic man, Mama ?
? Oh, he's a magic man ?
[rock song continues playing]
我们学校的所有女孩都爱上了崔普
[narrator] All the girls at our school were in love with Trip.
所有的女孩 除了勒克斯
All the girls except for Lux.
崔普说 他是从上错第五节历史课
Trip told us his passion for Lux Lisbon all started
开始迷上勒克斯的
when he went into the wrong history class during fifth period.
按照惯例 他在外边抽大麻
As was his custom, he went out to his car to smoke the marijuana
他像糖尿病童打胰岛素一样按时吸食大麻
he took as regularly as Peter Petrovich, the diabetic kid, took his insulin.
那一天 他为了躲伍德哈斯先生
On this particular day he ran into Mr. Woodhouse in the hall
溜进一间教室
and ducked into the nearest class.
她是这个旋转世界中的静点
[Trip] She was the still point of the turning world, man.
我从未忘记过她 从来没有
I never got over that girl.
Never.
我爱过很多女人 但跟那不一样...
I mean, you know, I loved a lot of ladies, but not like that.
那是真的
That was real.
我永远忘不了第一次见她
I'll never forget the first time I saw her.
我不知道是什么打动了我 我不知道该怎么办
I didn't know what had hit me.
I-I didn't know what to do.
因为与别的女孩总是得心应手
It was so easy with all the other girls.
但她看都不看我
But she wouldn't look at me.
我...我不是主动追人的类型
I, uh ―
I was never the kind to pursue, if you know what I mean.
如果你知道我的意思
她让我疯狂 伙计
That girl drove me crazy, man.
真好吃
- Mmm, yummy. Warm. - Mm-hmm.
勒克斯?
Hey, Lux.
嘿
Hey.
看看 只是面包片加肉而已
[Bonnie giggles] Look at him.
- It's just meat on bread. - Ew. Sick.
谢谢 妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
[laughing]
[slow R&B ballad playing]
[man] ? I can think of younger days ?
崔普的爸爸帮不上什么忙
[narrator] Trip's dad was little help.
[R&B ballad continues playing]
嗯 首先 别给她打电话
Well, first off, don't call her on the phone.
这... 很奥妙
It's all, um ― It's all subtlety.
有细微的差别
It's all nuance.
是的 你只要在学校跟她说说话
Yeah, yeah. You just need to talk to her at school, you know.
什么都行
About anything. About, uh, the weather or school assignments.
天气... 或作业
只要找到
Um, you know, anything to have the chance to communicate
用眼神交流的机会
with the language of eye contact.
还有对计划的信心
A-And, uh, project confidence.
别让头发挡着眼
And, uh, keep the hair out of your eyes.
感受那气氛
She'll feel the vibe.
? How can you mend ?
? A broken heart? ?
? Oh ?
做你自己就好了 对
- And be yourself. - Yeah.
- [dramatic music on soundtrack] - [wind howling]
"飓风"是自然界
[movie: narrator] The word "hurricane" is the name given to nature's strongest storm.
最强的风暴
当高压气团与低压气团相遇时
A hurricane occurs when high pressure and low pressure masses of air
就会形成飓风
come in contact with one another.
两种气团通常
There is often a significant difference in temperature between the two masses.
存在显著的气温差异
一种是暖的 另一种是冷的
One mass is warm, while the other is cold.
暖气团上升 冷气团下降
The warmer air rises and the cooler air falls.
同时 低压气团
Likewise, the low pressure area slides down the sides of the high pressure area.
从高压气团的边缘滑下
它们互相绕着彼此打转
They swirl in and around one another, creating the beginnings of the storm.
这就是风暴的开始
[thunderclap]
从这幅
In this footage, taken from US Navy weather patrol aircraft,
美国海军气象巡逻机拍的图象来看
我们可以发现
we can clearly observe the two masses ―
高低压气团
one high pressure and one low pressure ―
彼此接触了
coming in contact with one another.
- [wind howling] - [dramatic music continues]
结果产生了极具破坏性
The result is a surging storm of tremendous strength
而且强有力的大风暴
that strikes with forceful determination.
[thunder crashing, rumbling]
尽管飓风
Even though the hurricane is the most powerful storm known to all of us ―
是我们所知的最强风暴
它袭击大块陆地
- [loud fart] - [students laughing]
比如大洲或大的岛屿
as it strikes large land areas, such as continents or large islands,
而且消退缓慢
it slowly dies.
是蒙特顾马先生 他最恶心了
[whispering] That must've been Conley.
His ass is grass.
[dramatic music continues playing]
我想约你出去
I'm gonna ask you out.
没门
Fat chance.
[movie narrator continues, indistinct]
首先 我要去你家看电视 First, I’ll go over to your house and watch the tube.
First I'm gonna come over to your house on Sunday and watch the tube.
接着我会邀你出去 And then I’m gonna ask you out.
Then I'm gonna ask you out.
...resulting in few injuries and much less destruction
of public services and community functions
than this graphic footage would indicate.
你真是人间尤物
You're a stone fox.
飓风
The hurricane, one of the most truly awe-inspiring
大自然孕育出的
最壮丽的史诗之一
and spectacular storms nature has to offer.
[dramatic music ends]
这是几频道? 五
- [narrator on TV, indistinct] - [Mrs. Lisbon] What channel is this?
哦 来看看...
- [Lux] Five. - Ah, let's see.
"野生动物 穿越非洲卡拉哈里沙漠的旅行"
Um, "Animals in the wild.
Journey through the African Kalahari
"观赏自然栖息地中的动物"
as we visit exotic animals in their natural habitat."
我觉得听上去不错 你说呢?
I think that sounds very nice, don't you?
[narrator] Now to the southwest,
广大的雨林最终让位给了草原
this huge rain forest eventually gives way
to expansive, arid grasslands
它往四周无限延伸
that stretch to the horizon in all directions.
这就是卡拉哈里
This is the Kalahari.
想再要点可乐吗? 是的 当然 谢谢
Uh, do you want some more pop?
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
草原上的繁荣景象日渐衰竭
The wildlife spectacle played out on these vast, open grasslands
而休眠中的雨林
and in the deep recesses of the rain forest
将在世界各地苏醒
is unparalleled anywhere on Earth.
[growling, roaring]
勒克斯 把脚放下去
Lux, please put your feet down, honey.
[snickering]
卡拉哈里和浩瀚的苍穹
The Kalahari and its vast, open skies
为兽群以及猎食的
provide the theater for the elemental life-and-death drama
大型猫科动物
played out by the plentiful four-footed herds
上演的生死循环戏码提供了舞台
and the great hunting cats that prey on them.
哦 天哪!
[Mrs. Lisbon] Oh, my.
现在已经很晚了 亲爱的? let’s getting so late. Honey...?
I-I-It's getting so late. Honey?
我说已经很晚了
- Yeah. Oh! - I said it's getting late.
好的 把电视关了吧
Well, uh, Skip, we usually, uh, hit the hay about now, so...
[coughs]
是的 呃...
Right. Yeah.
好的 谢谢
- Okay. Okay. - Thank you.
很高兴见到你 里斯本太太 是的
- Okay, so... - It was nice to meet you, Mrs. Lisbon.
- Yes. - Thank you.
晚安 再见
- Good night. - See ya.
[Mr. Lisbon] Yeah. [sighs]
[narrator on TV continues, faint]
[exhales]
再见
Bye.
[slow acoustic guitar intro]
[acoustic guitar, quicker tempo]
[rock guitar, drums join in]
? If we still have time We might still get by ?
? Every time I think about it I wanna cry ?
? With bombs and the devil And the kids keep comin' ?
我得回去
- [song continues playing] - Gotta get back for bed check.
? No time to be young ?
? Well, I tell myself That I was doin' all right ?
? There's nothin' left to do tonight ?
? But go crazy on you ?
[footsteps]
[throat clears]
这是第四节课 你应该第五节课来 不是吗？
Uh, this is fourth period, Trip. I don't have you until fifth, do I?
我知道 我不是为数学来的 先生 l know. I’m not here for math today, sir.
- Uh, no. - Oh.
I'm not here for math today, sir.
我来告诉你 I’m here to tell you that
Look, I'm here to tell you that my intentions for your daughter are entirely honorable.
我对你女儿的意图是真心的
什么意图?
What might those intentions be?
邀勒克斯去校园舞会
I wanna ask Lux to the homecoming dance.
崔普 先坐下吧
Trip, why don't you sit down for a minute.
All right.
你知道 我妻子和我有明确的规则
You see, my wife and I have certain rules.
这约束了大女儿
They've been the same rules for the older girls,
我不能为了小女儿开先例
and I can't very well go and change them now for the younger ones.
就算我想 我妻子也不会同意的
Even if I wanted to, the wife wouldn't let me. [chuckles] It's true.
所以 如果你想再来看电视
So, uh, if you wanna come over and watch television again,
那可以
that would be fine.
但你不能带勒克斯出去 特别是乘车
But you cannot take Lux out, especially not in a car.
所以不好意思 年轻人 这是我们的规矩 So I’m sorry, son, that's just our policy.
So, I'm sorry, son. That's just our policy.
好的 先生 如果我们几个男孩
Okay, sir, what if ― what if there was a bunch of us guys
邀请你所有女儿们
and we took all your daughters out in a group
并在你规定的时间把她们送回去呢?
and we had 'em back by whatever time that you said?
你是橄榄球队的吗? 是的 先生
You on the football squad son?
什么位置? 四分卫
- Yes, sir. - Oh. What position?
Defensive corner back.
好样的
Ah. Well, uh, good. Good.
我以前... 我当年可是中卫
I was a ― [clears throat] I was a safety in my day.
嗯 那是个重要位置 先生
Well, that's a crucial position, sir.
得分全靠你了 不错!
- Nothing between you and the goal line. - Exactly. Exactly.
哦 好吧 是这样的 先生
- [school bell rings] - Uh, well...
我们有场比赛
So, the thing is, sir, we've got the big game against Country Day,
之后还有舞会
and then afterwards we have the dance and everything, and...
其他人都有舞伴了
like, all the other guys are taking dates.
你很帅 很多女孩愿意跟你出去
You're a good-looking fellow, Trip. Lots of girls would go with you, I bet.
我对她们不感兴趣 先生 I’m not interested in lots of girls, sir.
Yeah, well, I'm not interested in lots of girls, sir.
我会跟我妻子商量的 崔普 我尽量 I’ll take it up with the wife, Trip. Do what l can.
I'll take it up with the wife, Trip, do what I can.
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir.
这可是门手艺
- It's a classic. It's really dark. - Oh.
Mmm.
崔普・方汀和几个橄榄球队的男孩
Uh, Trip Fontaine and, uh, some of the other boys on the football squad
想带她们去校园舞会
have asked to take the girls to the homecoming dance.
你知道我对那个怎么想
- [gasping] - You know how I feel about that sort of thing.
我会保驾护航的 妈妈 拜托! I’m a chaperone at the dance. Oh, please!
But, dear, I'm gonna be a chaperone at the dance.
Oh, come on, Mom, please.
你爸爸和我等会儿再商量
Your father and I will discuss it later.
方汀先生 能跟你说句话吗?
Mr. Fontaine, may I speak with you, please?
关于你的请求 我和我妻子已经决定了...
[clears throat] Now, my wife and I have, uh, had a little talk,
and we've come to a decision about your request.
[no audible dialogue]
[Mr. Lisbon] Okay?
好极了!
Yes!
我要带勒克斯・里斯本去校园舞会 I’m taking Lux Lisbon to Homecoming.
- [exhales] - [whistle blows]
Taking Lux Lisbon to Homecoming.
我还需要三个人带其他几个女孩
All I need is three guys to take the other girls.
[whistle blows]
我给你三支大麻 崔普 I’ll give you three joints, Trip.
I'll give you three joints, Trip.
选我吧 我们可以开我爸的大众
Come on, Trip, man. You pick me, we can take my dad's Caddie.
你也得叫上我 崔普斯特
- [whistle blows] - You gotta pick me, Tripster.
崔普 伙计 你欠我的
Trip, man, you owe me.
我那次从伍德哈斯手里救了你一命
- I saved your ass with Woodhouse that time. - [whistle blows]
谢谢 爸爸 其他男孩是谁?
- [screaming] Oh, thanks, Dad! - Okay, okay, okay.
Who are the other boys?
我们看看 帕克・德顿 杰克・克拉尼
Uh, let's see. Parker Denton and Jake Conley.
他是个好学生
He's a very good student, dear. And, uh, uh, Kevin Head.
还有凯文・海德
谁带谁? 各凭本事吧
- Who's taking who? - Whom.
They're just gonna raffle us off.
女孩们选择哪件并不要紧
[narrator] It didn't make any difference which pattern of their dream dresses
the girls each chose.
里斯本太太在胸部加了一寸
Mrs. Lisbon added an inch to the bust line and two inches to the waist and hems.
腰部加了两寸
裙子变成了四个一样的麻袋
And the dresses came out as four identical sacks.
都准备好了? 是的
- Everybody decent? - Yeah.
好的 来吧
Okay, come on.
哦 抱歉 好了 Oh, I’m sorry. Here we go.
Oh, sorry. Okay, here we go. Okay, come on. Together.
好的 离近点
说茄子
- There's a leak. - And cheddar cheese.
- [laughs] - [coughs]
真兴奋!
I'm so excited.
You're in my way.
[tires squeal]
[engine off]
[exhales]
准备好了吗?       好了 伙计
- We ready? - Let's go.
Ready, man.
行动吧
Let's do it.
最后帕克因为那辆大众而胜出
[narrator] In the end, Parkie won because of the Cadillac,
凯文・海德因为超猛的大麻
Kevin Head because he had the killer weed,
还有周・黑尔・克拉尼 因为他获奖无数
and Joe Hill Conley because he won all the school prizes,
崔普认为这些能打动里斯本夫妇
which Trip thought would impress Mr. and Mrs. Lisbon.
你们好 男孩们       你好 里斯本太太
- Hello, boys. - [all] Hello, Mrs. Lisbon.
进来吧       谢谢
Come in.
Thank you.
谁开车?       是我
Uh, who ― who's driving?
你有驾照多长时间了?
I am.
How long have you had your license?
两个月 但我学了一年
Two months, but I had my learner's permit for a year before that.
她们几乎没有乘车出去过
You know, we ― we almost never allow the girls to go out in cars
unless it's necessary.
最近有很多车祸
There's so many accidents nowadays. I'm sure you will be very careful.
你们要小心       好的
好的 最后评估完毕
- Oh, yes, ma'am. - Okay, third degree's over.
女孩们!
Girls!
我得走了 舞会见 I’d better go. See you at the dance.
I better get going. I'll see you at the dance, huh?
到时见 里斯本先生
- See you there, Mr. Lisbon. - Okay.
再见 亲爱的
- Bye, dear. - [chuckles]
- See you later. - Yeah. Good.
女孩们 下来
Girls? Come on down.
男孩们来了
The boys are here.
我们选的白色 因为不知道你们要穿什么
We got white ones.
花店的人说白色百搭
We didn't know what you were wearing.
The guy, the flower guy, said that white would go with anything, so...
很高兴你选白色 I’m glad you got white.
I'm glad you got white.
为什么不帮她们别上呢?
[Mrs. Lisbon] Why don't you pin them on?
Yeah.
Here.
[all murmuring]
[Lux] Don't stick me.
- [laughing] - Almost, almost.
- This isn't... gonna work. - [chattering]
崔普
- Just ― [chuckles] - Popped off right away.
- Oh. - [laughing]
好了 好了       我们走吧
There we go. All right.
太好了
- Let's do it. - All right.
再见 妈妈
Bye, Mom.
Bye.
Hi.
上帝 看啊! 那辆车又停在那儿了!
Oh, my gosh. Look, you guys. Her car's there late again.
我确定李先生跟她有一腿 I’m sure Mr. Lea's having an affair with her.
[Bonnie] I'm sure Mr. Leo's having an affair with the maid.
我见过他跟着她进了洗衣室
I saw him follow her into the laundry room.
他那个红鼻子真可悲
[Therese] Ew! He's so fat, and that red nose.
可能是个酒鬼
- Totally an alcoholic. - Yeah, and what about the Hessens?
海兹家的人呢？你知道他们是纳粹
- You know they're Nazis. - They're Nazi sympathizers, Bonnie.
是纳粹的拥护者
他们在史沃兹小姐
They had a fit when the Schwartzmans tried to join the tennis club.
进网球俱乐部时大发雷霆
[laughing]
铝边侧线不错!他们真觉得这样没问题吗?
[Lux] Nice aluminum siding.
Do they really think that looks okay?
彼特丝先生从电视上订的
You know Mr. Kreigers ordered that from TV late at night.
那是巴蒂诺家的烧烤木桩
Look, it's the Baldinos' barbecue tree stump.
我从没见过他们在那上面烧烤!
I have never seen them barbecue on that thing.
事实上 那是鲨鱼老兵的逃生隧道
Actually, it's an escape tunnel for Sammy the Shark.
通向河边和他的快艇
It leads to a river where he keeps his speedboat.
保罗经常去
Yeah, I mean Paul goes down there all the time.
他可以从下水道去任何一家的地下室
He can get into anyone's basement through the storm sewers.
不可能! 是的
- No way. - Yeah.
[Bonnie] Cool.
爸爸会闻出来的 不会 我有薄荷糖
[Bonnie] Dad'll smell it on you.
No, I got mints.
他会闻到你衣服上的味
He'll smell it on your clothes.
我就说有人在厕所里抽烟 I’ll say they were smoking in the toilets.
I'll just tell him some kids were smoking in the bathroom.
死前先破个雏吧(烟圈) 真恶心
Don't let it die a virgin.
成熟点吧 克拉尼
- [Therese] That's gross. - Yeah, grow up, Conley.
[pop song intro playing]
[man] ? Run, sailing softly through the sun ?
? In a broken stone-age dawn ?
? You fly so high ?
? I get a strange magic ?
? Oh, what a strange magic ?
? Oh, it's a strange magic ?
? Got a strange magic ?
想跳舞吗? 当然
- Uh, do you wanna dance? - Sure.
? You're walking meadows in my mind ?
跳舞吗?
? Making waves across my time ?
? Oh, no ?
? I get a strange magic ?
? Oh, what a strange magic ?
天气真不错 是吧?
We've been having such lovely weather, don't you think?
是的 不错... 很好
Yeah.
Yeah, it's been nice.
? Got a strange magic ?
- ? Got a strange magic ? - [feedback hums]
晚上好 能请大家注意一下吗?
Good evening, everyone.
If I could have your attention for just a moment.
我希望大家能过的愉快 看起来正是如此
I hope you're all having a good time. Sure looks like it.
舞会委员会可是使出浑身解数
The dance committee headed by Sabrina Gonner really outdid themselves this time.
返校节舞王舞后的投票开始 I’d like to open the voting for Homecoming King and Queen.
I'd, uh, like to open the voting for homecoming king and queen.
投票箱就在那边 请投票
The ballot box is over at the refreshments table,
so please cast your votes,
随后我们将宣布结果
and we'll make the announcement in a little while.
谢谢
Thank you.
有人看到你过来吗? 没有
Did anybody see you come in?
你呢? 没有
No.
- What about you? - No.
你会喜欢的
- You'll love it. - [giggles]
蜜桃松子酒
[Trip's voice] Peach Schnapps.
漂亮女孩都喜欢
Babes love it.
[man] ? I'm not in love ?
? So don't forget it ?
? It's just a silly phase I'm goin' through ?
味道真好
[Lux] This stuff tastes really good.
? And just because ?
我不想要 谢谢
I don't want any, thanks.
拜托 就尝一下 尝一小口
Come on. Just a taste. A tiny taste.
别当乖乖女了
[Lux] Don't be such a goody-goody.
别咽下去
? I'm not in love ?
Don't swallow it.
? It's because ?
? I'd like to see you ?
? But then again ?
? That doesn't mean You mean that much to me ?
? I'm not in love ?
? No, no ?
? It's because ?
- [tapping on microphone] - [feedback hums]
大家请注意
[Woodhouse] Can I have everyone's attention, please?
请大家鼓掌欢迎 I’d like you to put your hands together
Thank you.
I'd like you all to put your hands together for this year's king and queen...
今年的舞王舞后...
崔普・方汀和勒克斯・里斯本
Trip Fontaine and Lux Lisbon.
- [applause] - [man] ? Some happy, some sad ?
- [cheering] - [laughing]
? Think of childhood friends ?
? And the dreams we had ?
? We lived happily forever ?
? So the story goes ?
? But somehow we missed out ?
All right, Luxie!
? On that pot of gold ?
? But we'll try ?
? Best that we can ?
? To carry on ?
[tempo, faster]
- [cheering] - ? A gathering of angels ?
? Appeared above my head ?
? They sang to me this song of hope ?
? And this is what they said ?
? They said, "Come sail away ?
? Come sail away ?
? Come sail away with me ?
? Come sail away, come sail away ?
? Come sail away with me" ?
这是我最快乐的时光! I’m having the best time!
I'm having the best time.
[balloons popping]
[song: instrumental break]
我们出去走走吧
[whispering] Let's go for a walk.
还是算了 我一会儿得回来 I’d better not. l've got to go back in a minute.
We better not. We've gotta go back in a minute.
我们可以盯着车
We can keep an eye on the car. It won't leave without us.
他们不会不等我们就走的
我爸爸...
My dad.
告诉他你要把皇冠放到柜子里
Just tell him you had to put your crown in your locker.
[crickets chirping]
看到那块草皮了吗? 嗯?
- Hey, you see that divot there? - Uh-huh.
我今天就在那儿放倒了那小子
That's where I reamed this guy today, man.
全防住了       真的吗?
Cross-body block.
- Really? - [grunts] Uh-huh.
可能他们跟你爸爸回去了吧?       未必
[Parkie] Maybe they went home with your dad.
I doubt it.
我们完了 是勒克斯 不是我们
- We're cooked. - Luxie is. We're not.
[panting]
谁有薄荷糖?
Does anyone have any mints?
抱歉 没有
- Sorry. - No.
再见 帕克
Bye, Parkie.
我们送你们到门口       不 不必了
We'll walk you to the door.
No, don't.
为什么不行?      真的不必了
Why not?
Just don't.
好的
Okay.
你会给我打电话吗?
Will you call me?
当然!
Uh, absolutely.
再见
- Bye. - Bye.
再见 再见
Bye.
[exhaling]
[dog barking in distance]
[birds chirping]
你还好吗? 你去哪儿了?
[Mr. Lisbon] Are you okay? Did you get hurt? What happened?
[Mrs. Lisbon] Where have you been?
看看你这个样子! 进屋去!
Where have you been? Whatever was ― We've been sick ―
[Mr. Lisbon chattering angrily]
[Mrs. Lisbon] Get in that house.
[door slams]
那晚我独自走回家了
[Trip's voice] I walked home alone that night.
不关心她怎么回去 很奇怪
I didn't care how she got home. It was weird.
我是说 我喜欢她 我非常喜欢她
I mean, I liked her. I liked her a lot.
但那晚在操场...
But out there on the field...
那就是另一回事了
It was just different then.
那是我最后一次见她
That was the last time I saw her.
你知道 大多数人从没尝过那种爱情
You know, most people will never taste that kind of love.
但至少我经历过一次 对吗?
But at least I tasted it once, right?
[bell chimes]
您应该去开六点钟的群会了
Time for your six o'clock group meeting.
对勒克斯的晚归
[narrator] Given Lux's failure to make curfew, everyone expected a crackdown.
大家都预料到了坏结果
但没人想到会如此惨烈
But few anticipated it would be so drastic.
女孩们被禁止上学
The girls were taken out of school,
里斯本太太
and Mrs. Lisbon shut the house in maximum security isolation.
以最大的安全措施封锁了她家
她不止不让女孩们上学
She had done more than just take the girls out of school.
那个星期天 在一场教堂说教后
That Sunday, arriving home from a spirited church sermon,
里斯本太太让勒克斯销毁她的唱片
Mrs. Lisbon commanded Lux to destroy her rock records.
快点!
Now.
但是 妈妈...
[crying] But, Mom.
我最后再说一遍 勒克斯
This is final, Luxie.
这不公平       我说快点
That's not fair!
I said, now.
[sighs]
就现在 勒克斯!
Now, Luxie!
[crying continues]
快点儿
Come on.
Hold on.
热吻乐队 请别让我这么做
KISS. Please don't make me do this.
烧了它
Burn it.
[crying continues]
妈妈 空中铁匠!
Oh, Mom. Aerosmith.
拜托 别让我这么做
- Come on. Please, don't make me burn this. - No.
拜托...
Please. [coughing]
什么味道?
[Bonnie] What's that smell?
好吧 先至此为止
[Mrs. Lisbon coughs] It's ― All right. Um, that'll do for now.
给我 给我
Give me these. Give me these.
我扔到垃圾箱里 I’ll put them in the trash.
I'll put them in the trash.
[coughing]
[chainsaw motor revving]
[man] Whoo-hoo! Whoo!
从此我们开始看见勒克斯
[narrator] This was around the time we began to see Lux
在屋顶跟不同男人做爱
making love on the roof with random boys and men.
她脱光了吗?       看不出来
- [Tim] What else? Come on. Is she naked? - [Chase] What's she doing?
对准
- [Parkie] You can't tell. Hold on. - [Tim] Get it focused.
别吵了 等轮到你再说
- You're pushin' it. What are you doing? - Will you stop?
他们在干什么?
- Wait your turn. - What are they doing?
他们在滚来滚去
[Parkie] They're rolling around up there.
等等 她在他上面
Let me see. Let me see. Off.
- Hold on. - [Chase] All right, come on.
他的手插在她头发里
And she's on him. And he's rubbing his hands through her hair.
让我看看       不 这是我的望远镜 瑞斯
- Let me have a look. - No. No, no.
It's my t ― It's my telescope, Chase.
好的 还有什么?
- [laughs] - [Tim] Yes, and what else?
那男人穿着汉堡屋的制服
Our male up there seems to be in a Burger Chalet uniform.
给我看看
[Tim] Let me see.
是啊谁知道下一个有艳遇的是谁
Is it ― Yeah, the Burger Chalet ―
You never think that those guys, you know, ever get lucky.
接着她问我 刚才的事算不算下流
She turns to me and asks me if I thought what we had just done was dirty.
我知道该怎么说 我说不是
I knew what to say. I said no.
接着她拉着我的手问"你喜欢我 是吗?"
Then she grabs my hand and goes, "You like me, don't you?"
我什么也没说 最好让小妞们猜测
I didn't say anything. You know, it's best to keep chicks guessing.
瑞斯 宝贝儿 晚饭前得练习小提琴
[woman] Chase, honey, come practice your violin before dinner.
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe it.
勒克斯今晚又上屋顶了!
Lux is on the roof again tonight.
她的手在下滑 我得看看
- Her hands are moving down. - I gotta see this.
太美了       现在是她在上面了
- Oh. - This is beautiful.
Now she's on top of him.
她在做什么 伙计?       等等
- What's she doin', man? - Wait.
现在做完了 他起来了
Now they're done. He's getting up.
就这样? 真是快
That's it?
That was quick.
...再加1 如果指数是时间
[sighs] "N" plus one, and, uh,
if the dimension is time, then you would have as your approach ―
那我们就有...
早安
Oh, good morning. Good morning ― [murmurs]
用光合作用做早餐了吗?
Have we photosynthesized our breakfast today?
[locker clattering]
[muttering]
你好 罗纳德 嗨 哈里
Hello, Ronald.
Hi, Eric.
你的女儿们已经两周没来上学了
Your daughters haven't been in school for over two weeks.
你查过了?
You checked out back?
他们找了个新数学老师
[Mrs. Buell] Dini Flasher said they found a new math teacher.
他得找新工作了 我知道
Well, he's gonna have to get another job, that's for sure.
I know.
女孩们还要这样被关多久?
How long can those girls be cooped up like that?
[motor revving]
走开 这是我们的树
Just go away. This is our tree.
女孩们 女孩们...为时已晚 这棵树已经死了
Girls. Girls, it's a little late.
为什么不让它自生自灭呢?
Okay, this tree is dead.
Why don't you just leave it up to nature?
那样所有树都会死
If we left it up to nature, there'd be no trees left.
反正最后结果也一样
[scoffs] That's what it's gonna be like anyway.
如果真菌没从欧洲扩散
If the boats didn't bring the fungus from Europe,
就不会这样了
none of this would've happened in the first place.
好的 走吧
Okay. Let's go.
不走?
No?
这样 我收到命令要砍掉你们的榆树
All right, that's it.
I have an order to cut down your elm tree, but your kids won't let us.
但你的孩子们不让
Dear?
你怎么知道树有病
- How do you know that tree's sick? - Believe me, we know.
相信我 它叶子都黄了
It had yellow leaves. The tree is dead, for Christ's sake.
真的死了 it’s dead for Christsake.
Are you familiar with Aritex? Our daughter showed us an article.
知道毒疗法吗
我女儿给我看的文章
- It's a less aggressive therapy. - And it doesn't work.
里说这创伤较小
没用
- Ah. - I leave that tree there,
要是把它留着 明年所有树都会死
早晚都会死嘛
they'll all be gone by next year.
Will be anyway... way things are going.
听着 我不想打电话给警察
Look, I don't wanna have to call the police.
我女儿站在自家草坪上
[Mrs. Lisbon] Our daughters are simply standing on their own front lawn.
这犯哪门子的罪?
Since when is that a crime?
[Mr. Lisbon] Uh ―
[chainsaw motor revving]
克里弗 看到那些穿睡衣的女孩了吗?
Clyde? Did you see those girls in the ― in the nighties?
就拍那儿 That's what I want. That’s the shot that l want.
That's what I want. That's the shot that I want. Okay?
亲爱的 再往前一点
Honey, you're gonna have to move forward. I want those girls in the nighties.
我想拍穿睡衣的女孩
Oh, God. Okay.
后面一点 放松点
Here, let's just back up a little bit here.
- [cameraman] Give me some slack. - There you go. Is that good?
好了 这样行吗? 好
- Okay? - Great.
去年引起国内一片哗然的
Four sisters of Cecilia Lisbon, the east-side teenager
东部自杀少女塞西利亚・里斯本
whose suicide last summer focused awareness on a national problem,
她的四个姐姐关注全国性的问题
不顾危险
put their own lives in jeopardy
想保护塞西利亚深爱的榆树
by trying to protect the elm that Cecilia so dearly loved.
[chainsaw motor whirring]
[birds chirping]
一阴天你的黑眼圈就很明显
[Mary] The circles under your eyes come out more when you're in overcast.
你得涂...
All right? So you need to wear more concealer when it's cloudy.
接下来的几个星期 我们基本见不到她们
[narrator] For the next few weeks, we hardly saw the girls at all.
乔依并没照约定给特瑞丝打电话
Joe Hill Conley didn't call Therese as he had promised.
So we need more colors.
勒克斯再也没跟崔普说过话
And Lux never spoke to Trip again.
[Mary] So, you should tone it down a bit. But in the shade ―
你真是人间尤物
[Trip's voice] You're a stone fox.
女孩们与世界的唯一联系
[narrator] The girls' only contact with the outside world
是她们订的杂志
was through the catalogs they ordered
她们的邮箱里
that started to fill the Lisbons' mailbox
充满了时尚图片
with pictures of high-end fashions and brochures for exotic vacations.
还有异国旅游手册
因为不能外出
Unable to go anywhere, the girls traveled in their imaginations
她们乘着想像游览暹罗神庙
to gold-tipped Siamese temples,
又或经过
or past an old man with a leaf broom tidying a moss-carpeted speck of Japan.
打扫满地青苔的日本老人
我们订了同样的杂志
We ordered the same catalogs,
与她们在蒙尘的小道上远足
and flipping through the pages, we hiked through dusty passes with the girls,
时不时停下
stopping every now and then to help them with their backpacks...
帮她们整理背包
将手放在她们温暖 湿润的肩膀上
placing our hands on their warm, moist shoulders,
共赏日落的余辉
and gazing off at papaya sunsets.
我们和她们一起在凉亭喝茶
We drank tea with them in a water pavilion.
我们随心所欲
We did whatever we wanted.
塞西利亚没有死 她是加尔各答的新娘
Cecilia hadn't died.
She was a bride in Calcutta.
无法实现的旅行
The only way we could feel close to the girls
是我们走近她们的唯一方法
was through these impossible excursions, which have scarred us forever...
那让我们铭记终生
这些梦比真实的女人更让我们快乐
making us happier with dreams than wives.
我们收集她们所有的东西
Collecting everything we could of theirs,
女孩们萦绕在我们脑海里
the Lisbon girls wouldn't leave our minds.
但她们在消逝
But they were slipping away.
她们眼睛的颜色渐渐淡去
The color of their eyes was fading, along with the exact locations of moles and dimples.
连同消失的酒窝
五个变成了四个
From five they had become four,
如行尸走肉般活着...
and they were all, the living and the dead,
变成了影子
becoming shadows.
如果她们没有联系我们
We would have lost them completely if the girls hadn't contacted us.
我们就彻底失去她们了
1长 2短
[Chase] Okay, one long.
Two short.
1长 记下了?
- And one long. - Mm-hmm.
就这样 好的
You got that? That's it.
Okay.
救助
Help.
送来
Send...
bo...
bo.
Bobo? Bobo 就是这个... Bobo
- Bobo? - Bobo.
I just ― Watch this.
"救助 送来Bobo" 我还以为你懂摩尔斯密码!
Bobo.
Help send bobo?
I thought you knew Morse code.
有东西给你
Something here for you.
记得我们吗? 你会帮忙吗? 给瑞斯
我也收到一张
[door closes]
I got one too.
亲爱的无论是谁 告诉催普我不爱他了 他是个混蛋
我们绞尽脑汁地想联系她们
[narrator] We racked our brains for a way of contacting them.
汤姆建议我们往她们家放风筝
Tom Fahey suggested we fly a kite with a message alongside the house,
上面绑上纸条
但这有逻辑上的错误
but that had logistical problems.
最后 答案很简单
In the end, the answer was so simple it took a week to come up with.
我们给她们打电话
We called them on the telephone.
- [line buzzing] - 727-8221.
8221.
准备
- [line ringing] - Get ready.
你好? 行动!
- [Mary] Hello? - Go.
嗨 是我
[man] ? Hello, it's me ?
我为你我的关系苦恼了很久
? I've thought about us For a long, long time ?
打给我们 7270487
Call us. 727-0487.
? But something's wrong ?
该死 是她们
- [phone rings] - Shit. It's them.
[pop intro playing]
回首昨日
[man] ? To think that only yesterday ?
我曾无忧无虑
? I was cheerful, bright, and gay ?
对无人知晓的未来
? Looking forward to who wouldn't do ?
和一切充满希翼
? The role I was about to play ?
危难之际
? But in my hour of need ?
我是真的 再次孤身一人 本就如此
? I truly am, indeed ?
? Alone again, naturally ?
投入我怀抱 当你孤单的时候
[men] ? Run to me whenever you're lonely ?
投入我怀抱 每当你需要依靠
? Run to me if you need a shoulder ?
某些时刻 你的他应该成熟而可靠
? Now and then You need someone older ?
那么 宝贝 来到我的怀抱
? So, darling ?
遥远的彼岸
[woman] ? So far away ?
是否仍有人原地驻足
? Doesn't anybody stay in one place Anymore? ?
看到你出现在门前 很幸福
? It would be so fine To see your face at my door ?
却无从得知 你将时光虚度
? Doesn't help to know ?
? You're just far away ?
我要回家了 明天见       回见 I’m going home. See you tomorrow.         See you later.
I gotta go home. See you tomorrow.
I'll see you later.
我们快窒息了 勒克斯      你在这儿很安全
- [Mrs. Lisbon] I'm-I'm just perplexed. - [Lux] We're suffocating.
我没法呼吸
- You're safe here. - I can't breathe in here.
没人接
No answer.
[motor whirring in distance]
- [whirring continues] - [crushing sound]
明天午夜 等我们的信号
几点了?       到时候了
- [Tim] What time is it? - [Chase] Anytime now.
伙计们 就在那儿       是吗?
- Guys, there it is. - What?
是的 是她们
[Tim] Yeah, it's them.
我们走
- Let's go. - Let's go.
我有我妈的车钥匙
[whispering] I got the keys to my mom's car.
- [clattering] - Shh!
Shh.
也许我们该敲敲门
[Tim] Maybe we should knock.
Yeah.
[knocking]
我们到了
We're here.
[door opens]
到点了 我们在等你们呢
About time.
We've been waiting for you guys.
我们有车 装满了油 想去哪儿都行
We got a car. We got a full tank of gas. We'll take you anywhere you wanna go.
是辆美洲豹 车厢很大
It's just a Cougar, but it's got a pretty big trunk.
我能坐前排吗? 当然
Can I sit up front?
Sure.
谁挨着我坐?
Which one of you is gonna sit up front next to me?
你父母在哪儿?       睡觉
Where are your parents?
你姐妹们呢? 马上就来
Asleep.
What about your sisters?
They're coming.
快点 很晚了
Come on. It's getting late.
再等5分钟
Wait five minutes. We had to wait until my parents were asleep.
得等我父母都睡着
得再等会儿 我妈失眠
They take forever.
My mom's an insomniac.
最好开我们的车 空间大些
We better take our car. There's more room.
你开得了旅行车吗?
Think you can handle a station wagon?
当然 又不是手动档 是吧?
Sure.
是的 没问题
- It's not a stick, is it? - No.
Yeah, no problem.
我能驾驶吗?       当然
Will you let me steer?
我们得走了 我听到有动静 可以是你妈妈
Sure.
But maybe we should get out of here. I just heard something.
- It could be your mom. - Come on in.
进来吧
我去车里等 I’ll go wait in the car.
I'll go wait in the car.
你们在这儿等她们吧
You guys wait here for my sisters.
[Lux laughing]
[humming]
[laughing]
[clattering]
[laughing quietly]
- [clattering] - Oops. These girls make me crazy.
只要摸到一个 就能让我疯狂!
If I could just feel one of 'em up just once.
怎么了?
What?
[hissing sound]
我们永远无法弄清发生的顺序
[narrator] We would never be sure about the sequence of events.
到现在我们还在讨论
We argue about it still.
很可能 邦妮死时
Most likely Bonnie had died while we were waiting in the living room,
我们正在客厅里
幻想着高速公路
dreaming of highways.
随后玛丽把头伸进了烤箱里
Mary put her head in the oven shortly thereafter.
特瑞丝吃了很多安眠药
Therese, stuffed with sleeping pills, was gone by the time we got there.
在我们到之前就走了
勒克斯是最后一个
Lux was the last to go.
[coughs]
[engine idling]
现在是周日下午四点钟
It's four o'clock on Sunday afternoon.
你知道你的孩子在哪儿吗?
Do you know where your children are?
邦妮 是里斯本姐妹中最小的一个...
Bonnie, the youngest Lisbon sister, strangely wore a 1920s wedding dress.
特瑞丝・里斯本 她很爱马 曾经写信...
Therese Lisbon, a horse lover, had written to the Brown University admissions office ―
玛丽想当啦啦队长
Yeah, Mary always wanted to be a cheerleader, but her mother wouldn't let her,
但她妈妈不同意
so I was teaching her the cheers.
在她们的家中自杀...
我愤怒到无以复加
[overlapping voices]
...莉迪亚・皮尔 八频道新闻
This has been Lydia Perl
with Channel 8 news.
我的女儿们并不缺少爱
[Mrs. Lisbon] None of my daughters lacked for any love.
我们家里有足够的爱
There was plenty of love in our house.
我就是弄不懂为什么
I never understood why.
[engine starts]
自杀事件后
[narrator] After the suicide free-for-all,
里斯本夫妇放弃了
Mr. and Mrs. Lisbon gave up any attempt to lead a normal life.
过正常生活的愿望
他们让海德力先生收拾了房子
They had Mr. Headley pack up the house,
把能卖的家具都贱卖了
selling what furniture he could in a garage sale.
里斯本先生把房子卖给一对波士顿年轻夫妇
Mr. Lisbon put the house on the market, and it was sold to a young couple from Boston.
当然
We, of course, took the family photos that were put out with the trash.
我们从垃圾堆里拣来了家庭相册
最终 我们拼凑出了谜团的答案
In the end, we had pieces of the puzzle,
但裂痕仍在
but no matter how we put them together, gaps remained.
形状奇怪的空白
Oddly shaped emptiness mapped by what surrounded them.
在环绕之物的映射下
就像叫不出名字的国度
Like countries we couldn't name.
[clock ticking]
徘徊在她们身后的并非生命
What lingered after them was not life...
而是现实生活中最琐碎的物件
but the most trivial list of mundane facts.
墙上滴答作响的钟摆
A clock ticking on the wall.
正午昏暗的房间
A room dim at noon.
人类自私的暴行
The outrageousness of a human being thinking only of herself.
自行其道
我们开始徒劳的试图忘记她们
We began the impossible process of trying to forget them.
[ticking continues]
我们的父母做能的更好
Our parents seemed better able to do this,
他们回到网球组和鸡尾酒会上
returning to their tennis foursomes and cocktail cruises
处变不惊
as though they'd seen this all before.
盛夏又到来了
It was full-fledged summer again,
在塞西利亚割腕一年后
over a year from the time Cecilia had slit her wrists,
空气中充满了毒药
spreading the poison in the air.
疯长的植物增加了湖里的磷肥
A spill at the plant increased the phosphates in the lake
并产生大量藻类
and produced a scum of algae so thick that the swamp smell filled the air,
沼泽的气味
环绕着这座气派的公馆
infiltrating the genteel mansions.
少女们初登社会
Debutantes cried over the misfortune of coming out in a season
每个人却只记得那时的恶臭
everyone would remember for its bad smell.
而奥康纳家人的别出心裁
The O'Connors, however, came up with the ingenious solution
给女儿爱丽丝的
of making the theme of their daughter Alice's debutante party
成人派对命名为"窒息"
asphyxiation.
像大家一样
Like everyone else, we went to forget about the Lisbon girls.
我们渐渐忘了里斯本家的女孩
她会让他心脏病发的
[chattering, laughing]
嗨 帕克
[chatters]
[retching]
会装死的虫子如何?
Al's got the, uh, acting bug.
我从檎基抓来的
She caught it from Pinkie.
我今晚想宣布
And I wanna announce tonight that next fall,
下个秋天 爱丽丝就要去纽瀚文上学了
Alice is going to a little school in New Haven.
我听说那里的语法学校十分了得
I hear they have a great drama school.
事实上 就是萨姆的爸爸建的 是吧?
In fact, Sam, I think your father built it, didn't he?
是医院 保罗
- [Sam] That's the law school. - [chuckling]
我们十分为爱丽丝自豪 万分自豪
We're so proud of Alice. We really couldn't be prouder.
这杯敬她
- [woman] Aw. Cheers. - [crowd] Cheers.
我受够了 再见 残酷世界
I've had it.
Good-bye, cruel world.
不 不 不! 你不会理解我的
No, no, no. You don't understand me.
我是少年 我有烦恼 I’m a teenager, l got problems.
I'm a teenager. I got problems.
[laughter]
这些年来 有许多关于她们的流言蜚语
So much has been said about the girls over the years...
但我们从未找到过答案
but we have never found an answer.
这与她们的早逝无关
It didn't matter in the end how old they had been...
[lighter flicking]
抑或因为她们是女孩
or that they were girls.
只因为我们爱过她们
But only that we had loved them...
她们始终听不见
and that they hadn't heard us calling,
我们在门外的呐喊
still do not hear us calling them out of those rooms...
她们始终在那里孤独着
where they went to be alone for all time...
我们永远无法将它们拼贴完整
and where we will never find the pieces to put them back together.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
[man] ? I'm a high school lover ?
? And you're my favorite flavor ?
? Love is all ?
? All my soul ?
? You're my playground love ?
? Yet my hands are shaking ?
? I feel my body remains ?
? Times don't matter ?
? I'm on fire ?
? On the playground, love ?
? You're the piece of gold ?
? That flashes on my soul ?
? Extra time ?
? On the ground ?
? You're my playground love ?
? Anytime ?
? Anyway ?
? You're my playground love ?